all right so in week seven of doing what
nobody has ever done before we're gonna
turn one of these hundred dollars into a
million dollars everything is gonna be
documented here on my YouTube Instagram
telegram Discord so not only you guys
can learn from my mistakes but also
follow the journey along we started six
weeks ago where I took my first attempt
at it but I blew the account then I gave
it another shot at it where then I
turned 100 to about 155 the 155 to about
a thousand a thousand to six thousand
six thousand to nineteen thousand
roughly then we did 19 000 to 48 000 and
then we did the 48 000 to 78 000 and now
this week where I'm gonna try and turn
in these 46 000 to 80 000 so let's let
the series begin let's get started
all right so we are ready for today it
is Sunday we got the toilet paper ready
the shit's about to go down this week
because the account right now is at 46
000. so it's crazy how we've stuck in
this from 100 to where it is now and
it's obviously been what like almost two
months now so this week shit's getting
serious that's why we got the toilet
paper so let me show you guys what I got
for this week all right so it is
currently Sunday as of right now and
this is my prediction for the week we
have GBP CAD which you guys saw in last
week's video how we caught a buy Here
gave us the majority of these profits
caught this by here which made back the
losses on this Wick out that we had
right here which is actually crazy we
got Wicked out by a pip we took another
buy here we took a buy Here buy here
we've absolutely been murdering GBP cat
because I haven't seen what I've been
doing here just go look at the series of
the 100 to the mill so then what I'm
expecting for this week to happen right
now on GBP CAD it's more of a lower time
frame thing I'm expecting for price to
do three steps before taking the trade I
caught a three-step before entering so I
need price to come into here drop down
into this area once it drops down into
this area I then need to break this
structure level and then I needed to
come back and then retest so this is one
two and then three this is where then I
will be entering my trade if I get my
confirmation signal with my strategy and
if you notice if that happens I'm
literally taking the same trade as I did
here and the same trade that I did here
the same trade that I did here it's the
same thing right prices at the same zone
I'm just gonna keep doing the same thing
because clearly it's working because
right now I love how it's looking but I
have to wait for my shift of structure
and confirmation that's GBP CAD for my
number one player for the week secondly
is AUD USD so we might have a trade that
comes in London session tonight as you
can tell we have the weekly time frame
bearish we are retesting this area of
Interest right here daily time frame is
bearish and we have retested and
rejected this area of Interest right
here beautiful daily bearish engulfing
doji uh can Candlestick and then the
four hour has shifted bearish where now
we are retesting the neckline of this
zone right here so in order for me to
enter this trade I'm going to wait for a
strong bearish confirmation Candlestick
which is going to be a bearish
Candlestick like this if we get a nice
solid bearish Candlestick bring it under
the structure at the right time session
then I will be looking for my stop loss
will be up right around here and my
first take profit will be right around
down here because I need a minimum of a
one to two risk to reward we gotta at
least be able to break under this zone
right here in order for me to be
entering this trade to the downside so
something to keep in mind because it
might be ready tonight in London session
so we might not start we might start off
the week fast next is GBP USD we
absolutely caught this last week
insanely like if you look over here to
my free telegram you guys can see here
how I actually predicted this
beautifully I sent this on August 31st I
literally said look at it we got 80 000
members in the free telegram watching it
I said break in and retest I update it
then as soon as it broke on the next uh
session and then on September 1st which
is the next day you see how it played
out perfectly and now we're here so I'm
going to be calling it again we already
called this perfectly we already caught
this so now I'm going to be waiting for
well we caught it but I didn't get to
enter it so now I'm gonna wait up for a
pull back into here to then take the
trade short
I'm going to be waiting for my bearish
engulfing Candlestick confirmation in
order for me to enter this trade to the
downside next we have your USD which is
the same exact thing we got to pull back
into this area in order for us to then
look for a cell which is very similar as
GBP USD and that is pretty much it all
these other pairs will kind of be ready
like later on throughout the week so
make sure you guys stay tuned to this
video we're on week seven we're about to
be two months into this Challenge and
there's a lot of markets with a lot of
good opportunity and if we do it right
we can probably even surpass our goal
this week of adk so stay tuned and if I
don't see you later in London I'll see
you guys in New York in the morning all
right what is up guys good morning so it
is 9 30 in the morning the next day so
let me show you guys how the market is
obviously the account is exactly the
same I'm almost taking the trade but I'm
kind of being a little bit more reserved
due to the fact that it is a bank
holiday today so let's check it out so
account is still the same 46 then we got
46 over here so let me show you guys the
markets right so GBP CAD yesterday was
dissipating how I wanted price to then
come down into this level to then reject
and then have the shift to structure
right we wanted the three point thing to
happen we're going to press to do the
one
two and then three to then head to the
upside price did not do that it just
decided to head straight to the upside
it is what it is we missed it but it was
a perfect Market entry right here and
it's exactly what I explained how it's
the same thing that we did here same
thing that we did here and the same
thing that we did here because it's the
same exact Zone and we're still bullish
on all time frames so it is what it is
next we have AUD USD which is exactly
what I explained yesterday I just threw
this out here yesterday so yesterday I
was expecting for price to come into
here and then reject and that is exactly
what we're doing as of right now but if
you noticed last night I drew out this
line right here literally last night and
I explained the only way I will enter
this trade is if it comes here breaks
and retests the zone so we are actually
creating a beautiful left head and then
a right shoulder at this area of
interest but we do have to keep in mind
today is a bank holiday but I don't
really pay attention to all the stuff
that much I really don't care I'm just
gonna keep waiting for the same exact
thing something like this that looks
very clean in order for us to take this
straight to the downside
I do like the inverted Head and
Shoulders but I don't like the fact that
it is just too fast in my opinion but
even if we do enter at this brake and
recess right here there is still plenty
of downside potential and still plenty
of upside profits that we can make so
AUD USD remains exactly the same and it
looks like it's loading up GBP USD we
have made it to the area of interest and
then we have had our first rejection
from this area and I like this because
it's kind of creating almost like a
double top and then on the 15 minute
it's creating a left head and then a
right shoulder but very similar like AUD
USD in order for me to enter this trade
I had to wait for the actual retest of
this Zone and the retest of the actual
neckline of the area of Interest so
we've already kind of done step one
which is make it to this zone right here
so we've already made it to that zone
now we gotta wait for the market to kind
of you know do its thing
next and last is Euro USD which we are
waiting for price to come into this area
as well we haven't quite made it there
so we're simply just you know waiting
for that and let me actually just skim
through these other markets and yeah
none of these are ready yet all right
perfect so yeah so everything Remains
the Same as last night the only one that
kind of took off was GDP CAD but it is
what it is we'll probably get another
entry on it very soon so it is currently
right now I'll show you guys 9 46 in the
morning so I'll be updating you guys in
the next hour or two depending on what
the market does so check it so Margaret
up this so it is currently 10 30 at
night so we ended up catching the AUD
USD trade exactly as I explained I could
have taken it earlier this morning but
you know I'd rather play it safe so I
just recently took it I think about an
hour ago so let me show you this this is
where the account is currently sitting
right now so it's 10 30 at night as you
can see this is where we are on the tray
right now I went very very low risk on
the trade I could have gone probably 30
35 risk but I went anywhere from like 23
to 24 risk because we can scale in and
position it on this Trace let me show
you so you guys can tell earlier this
morning or earlier this week actually I
was saying the only way I would sell is
if we break under this level right here
so at the beginning of the week we were
anticipating the pull back into this
area right here which we had it
perfectly to exactly where I wanted to
we had a beautiful rejection
candlesticks and I was explaining this
morning how I was ready to enter it at
the retest of the neckline of the head
and shoulders and then if you notice we
got a beautiful retest right here but if
you look at the time zone that is not in
the time zone where we like to take
trades so then I just simply waited for
them this break of structure right here
which it broke this neckline of the head
and shoulders I was actually a little
bit scared I thought this was going to
have a deeper pull back into here and I
was going to go into drawdown but
obviously price ended up playing very
nicely we are currently up right now
decent amount of profit not much in the
account percentage-wise but if we hit up
our take profit all the way down here we
should probably gain like another 20 30
on the account and then if we end up
pulling back tonight there in London I
will then add a position here and then
continue to sew to the downside so this
is this trade right here we predicted
perfectly GBP CAD we never pulled back
it is what it is it just continued
taking off to the upside GBP USD is
having the rejection now so we might add
some entries in GBP USD once it does the
same exact thing that AUD USD just did
and that is break and retest under this
structure level right here this is going
to be a double top formation but if you
notice this broke under that structure
level and that's why we entered this
right here has to break under that
structure level in order for us to sell
and then Euro USD simply never made it
all the way back up to our area of
Interest right here so we simply can't
take a trade so that's where we are
right now in the challenge looking
pretty solid so you guys can tell
10 30 at night and we are currently
floating about 11
000 in profit uh I'm gonna probably stay
up because I'm actually really tired
I've been setting up London every single
day probably for like the past what like
the past like month and a half so I
might stay up until London I might just
close it out and then I just caught up
and trade there you know we pretty low
risk trade and there's still plenty of
time throughout the week for me to hit
my goal of adk this week so let's see if
I stay up there in London if I hold it
or if I close I will update you guys all
right what's up guys good morning I have
to do this train of the past because
this thing is fluctuating and I gotta
code because we're at our take proper
right now so it'll show you guys this
trade is floating in profit thirty two
thousand dollars we're just up 38 000
which is giving eighty five thousand
dollars a profit this is how the trade
is right now I'm just hurrying up I'm
literally losing out on profit right now
just to show you guys this trade right
now so you know I'm putting you guys
first report
so Trey where I ended up doing that
tonight I just kept celebrating go after
one night it is currently 8 43 in the
morning and the exactly is uh but right
now we did not get the fullback that I
was participating last night uh to reset
this area right here we just kept it
into the town side but we might get the
pullback right now all right guys I'm
literally just waiting for it to hit 80
000 so I can close it because I have to
There Was 80 000 because that is my goal
for the week oh oh yeah almost there all
right so that was a little crazy like
intro right there I had to act fast on
the guys in the market was moving like
this New York session is about to open I
talked really fast and uh I always put
you guys first so you guys can see the
transparency and the legitimate part
about it I could have totally just
pulled back into the last time
I'm doing this for you guys so yeah so
that's it
one trade for the week and we've had
eight hours goal and we want no risk
wow wow
[Music]
so I mean now what I'm gonna do is I'm
just gonna be more conservative right I
don't have to take a trade anymore for
the week in order for this challenge to
be compete accordingly plus keep in mind
there's some very very solid traits to
the side and this let me actually show
you but I obviously missed but this is
AD guy that we just caught but then I
missed GBP USD remember how I was
anticipating yesterday gpsd to come into
this area around here and then sell well
if you guys notice that has happened but
I simply missed it because I was just
sleeping last night there in London and
it's okay because we ended up crashing a
the USB you know if you can't catch them
all uh your USD pulled back and never
hit our area of Interest so we were
never able to take the trick and then
GDP CAD like I have been saying it kind
of has to come back and create that work
so now it's doing that market update so
it is currently nine o'clock at night
and then kind of crazy we didn't have to
close the trade in a rush this morning
we could we're gonna still been holding
the trade I would have been making more
money that is the power upset again it's
that simple but it's okay we hit our
profit Target and I learned this lesson
not get greedy and just you know if that
was my goal for the trade my goal for
the week close it there so I've been
debating all day whether I keep on
trading for the week or if I completely
stop because if I stop right now this
YouTube series or this YouTube video for
week seven is gonna be super short it's
gonna be like five minutes and we have a
whole week ahead of us of still plenty
of marketing opportunities so I was
talking to the guys in the Discord I was
talking to the Traders on Instagram and
then it's just like if the trades in the
trade's there and if it's not it's not
but if I do take it take a little risk
right and I'm like you know what oh of
it I could deal with that because
realistically if the opportunity is
there I gotta take it and if it's not
there obviously I don't take it but I
can't kind of miss out on those good
opportunities even though I did hit my
target for the week but then like this
is where just like the mentality of the
trader comes in but it's like well then
if you break your rules of wanting to
get more for the week then you're
getting greedy because I'm supposed to
stop this week at 80k and the next week
is my goal would be 160 because I
doubled up then but then comes back to
the mentality where I'm like well what
if you just make it up to like 100 then
it's easier for next week and this is
where Traders drive themselves crazy
you're just putting all these different
types of scenarios in your head that's
kind of what's been going through me you
know like yes even though I've you know
turned 100 to 80k right now but I do
face challenges right I'm Still Human at
the end of the day so what I the
conclusion I came to it's like I my goal
is to not trade for the rest of the week
but I'm gonna keep watching the market
meaning I need to keep being in sync
with the market and if I see a triple A
Plus trade setup I would take it at a 10
to 15 risk and I'm personally okay with
that so let me show you guys how it
looks as of right now the account is
currently at 81 000 exactly the same you
guys can see it is nine o'clock uh Miami
time so this is the trade from earlier
today
earlier today we closed the trade right
around on top of this area here and the
market has continued to dip so we closed
it right around this area and it has
just kept heading to the downside my
analysis for it is that I do believe
that this has plenty of potential to
come back and then re-test this area
here to then keep heading to the
downside I do believe the four hour has
room to do that even though it didn't I
do believe it can't do that so I'm going
to put my next alarm at this point right
here so it notifies me around
psychological level 64
000. that's kind of crazy I didn't even
try to do that I just threw the alarm
and landed around psychological it's
kind of crazy but whatever next we got
is GBP CAD which it has Wicked into the
area that we've been anticipating for
the beginning of the week if you see
creating the wick so we have done that
we have done the beautiful daily
rejection Candlestick and I'm telling
you right now we're gonna do this again
we've done it once we've done it twice
we almost did it three times we we did
it four five and six times at this same
exact zone so now we got our seventh
potential entry coming in now you know
what to say about Lucky Seven so what
I'm going to be waiting for in order to
enter this trade is going to be
extremely simple I just need a retest of
this area right here
in order for price to come into it and
then we will get our entry signal to
head to the upside so I'm going to be
waiting for the pullback of this area of
Interest right here so we're no longer
going to be creating the wick we're
going to be creating
higher low
creating higher low in this area to then
head to the upside this is where I'll be
interested in my lungs and we're going
to do it again again and again so then
next we have GBP USD which we predicted
this perfectly at the beginning of the
week the break the retest but we just
you know didn't manage to enter this
trade I do believe that this next daily
Candlestick is going to now come back
and weaken to this zone right here so
let me just delete these unnecessary
zones I do believe this is going to pull
back and weaken to here before heading
to the downside so if I were to put an
area of Interest it kind of looks
something like this a very clean box
overpriced can then pull back and if you
notice if I drag this box to the left
it's used as resistance support support
and now it can potentially be used as
resistance so I'm going to be waiting
for this trade even though it's kind of
already doing it uh it's already having
the retest I kind of need to do it I
need for it to do it again I need to do
it on this daily Wick so we're going to
be potentially waiting for this to come
back and then re-test here and yeah Euro
USD never made it to the area of
interest but the direction of the market
was overall correct so we're going to be
waiting for GBP CAD to weaken to buy
and then we're going to be waiting for
this to then pull back right now so
it's Tuesday we still got plenty of time
left in the week is it Tuesday
it's Tuesday night
it's Tuesday night so
Tuesday night better be Wednesday we'll
check in tomorrow
all right so trade update so it is
currently 9 30 in the morning and the
trade that I explained yesterday on GBP
CAD has happened technically to
Perfection we just entered the trade now
so long ago uh let me show you guys a
second so you guys can see we are
literally in the trade right now we are
right around break even I went very very
low risk on this trade because I didn't
have to take the trade like I already
hit my take profit for the goal I'm kind
of doing this more for the series so
like it's not a five minute video and
honestly it's a good trading opportunity
and I don't need to risk the 33 that I'm
usually going to risk so I risked I
think it's like four or five percent on
the trade so let me explain let me show
you guys so the trade right now is
literally right our entry yesterday we
were expecting for price to have a pool
back into this level in order to come
back and retest this area of interest to
then head to the upside so we've had a
huge reaction from that point right
there and now we are currently having a
pullback right back into our entry level
I have a pretty big stop loss if you
notice it's kind of learning from my
mistakes over here how I've gotten
Wicked out on all these zones over here
and then I kind of put it way under this
zone right here so as of right now we're
entering a little bit of drawdown
um no big deal I do think it might fit
that Wick if this body does close under
this structure point I might just close
the trade as a whole uh but this is how
we're currently looking on the account
on GBP CAD AED USD is kind of looking
like what I explained yesterday uh well
no actually pretty much what I explained
yesterday price is going to pull back
into this area right here and then we're
gonna have our cell if we come and
reject office area which that is what we
are currently doing I personally would
love in order for us to enter this trade
for this trade to do a very simple break
and retest of this area of interest if
you see we have resistance we have
support I then need price to then have
something like this in order for me to
enter this trade to the downside GBP USD
has pulled back to the area of Interest
as well
started having a reaction not really
paying attention to honestly my main
focus is on GBP Cad and it is on AUD USD
So currently right now it is so I'll
show you guys 9 25 in the morning uh
Wednesday let's just wait for the swipe
to unlock thing to leave
um well do you guys see right there
Wednesday 9 25 in the morning so update
you guys how we looking on the account
if I lose this trade I think it's a
couple thousand dollars not that much
currently down
200 bones all right guys so trade update
we got stopped out on the trade we're on
the phone right now because the camera
has no battery but literally look at
this crazy Canada we just got absolutely
murdered like this is crazy it is what
it is a good thing I went low risk I
might be done trading for the week and
it's kind of kind of annoying because
missed out on the trade that I have been
calling on GBP USD I've been missing out
on these sales since point one up here
since 0.2 Right Here and Now 0.3 again
we caught this break and retest
perfectly earlier this week as well with
AUD USD we caught this cell earlier this
week but now we've had the retest of the
area of interest and now it's sending
off pretty much exactly as I explained
then
yeah it is what it is now we're having
the break of this Candlestick and it's
currently right now as you can see it is
10 42 in the morning so about an hour
since the last time we updated so I'm
going to be waiting for a little retest
of this area to then maybe add a trade
sure I honestly just might be done for
the week
um Just Gonna Keep just doing my thing
you know I'm gonna keep being very
selective so yeah trade up this is what
happened
it is what it is it's part of the
process can't avoid this kind of stuff
happening like
I'm very glad I went low risk which is a
good thing that's very intelligent of me
and now I just analyze learned from my
mistakes and I move on so all right so
market update it is currently Wednesday
night about to be midnight so let me
show you guys the trade that we took
earlier this morning how it murdered the
stop loss completely and on top of that
how the trade that I predicted then I
ended up taking it so let me show you
this is the account where we currently
are right now so we're down about 3K
almost from where we originally were
earlier this morning good thing I went
low risk on the trade but let me show
you guys what went down right so
obviously we have taken one two three
four five six buys at the same exact
zone right here this is where we've made
the majority of the profit on this
account that's taken us to about 78k so
now when price comes back into here I
just expected to do the same thing how
it did six times so that shows you right
there the seventh time the lucky number
from the casino that's [__] it's a
trap shows you right here because this
is seven times it comes back and it
doesn't reject so we've completely
broken through the zone and now we've
made it now to this snare this next area
of inches here which if you see over
here we've caught on a buy here as well
but I don't like the fact of how the
daily Candlestick has closed very
aggressively to the downside so I'm
going to stay away from this marker for
now uh AUD USD which is the market that
we caught earlier uh this week which
basically gave us the profit for the
week we have retested to the area of
Interest perfectly as we wanted to I do
like how it's looking on the lower time
frames I do love how it basically broke
and retested the zone as I was
anticipating I'm going to wait to see if
now this comes back and creates a lower
high on the lower time frame like the 15
minute and if it comes in and it rejects
around this Zone maybe even back up into
here to around 63 800 I will then be
waiting for an entry signal like this a
bearish engulfing confirmation to then
take this trade to the downside which is
going to be very very key because I can
probably just go low risk again and then
make back the little profit foods that
have been lost so I can stay at the adk
for the week but this trade I do believe
it has some downside potential because I
do like how the daily has close and then
on top of that we have GBP USD which
this is just absolutely insane like this
we've been calling it since the high
point right here if you guys look here
in the free telegram literally sent it
on September 4th you guys can see how it
was at that point right there that is
that point right there beautiful cells
to the downside exactly what I explained
we then anticipated a pullback here
happened exactly how I explained then
you had another drop and then if we go
down on the one hour the zone that I had
marked off broke everything happened
perfectly we just didn't manage to take
it my analysis now is pretty much done I
do believe this might then pull back
into this area to then go to the
downside but I'm just not like 100 sure
about it so I'm just going to stay away
from this market and strictly just put
my energy on AUD USD if it does what I'm
looking for GBP CAD it's been fun but
for now I want to stay away okay and so
we don't at least make it above this
Zone and then pretty much uh Euro USD
didn't make it back all the way to the
area of interest that we expected but it
did have the push and then every other
Market just simply not interested so
right now only going to be waiting for
AUD USD to have a pullback to around
this Zone around here so I'm going to
put my alarm so it notifies me so then I
be interested in entering the shirts
around this area and then it's pretty
much it because DBP CAD is gone so AUD
is D is going to be the only one so
we'll update you guys tomorrow in the
morning if I don't end up taking the
trade tonight they're in London which it
might present itself so current market
update it is currently 11 45 Wednesday
see what happens all right so trade
update so we're currently right now
we're gonna keep it skein came to the
beach it is Thursday three o'clock
so we pulled up before traffic got a
little bit here late because we took a
nap mark is not doing anything let's go
to the beach with the boys saskatchew
Vibes we're gonna go there now got
Jordan driving the roads
wearing this repair by the way best gas
station snack mini Chips Ahoy the only
thing don't get chips
Chips Ahoy all right so market update
let me check my phone
ah
harbino on a serious note uh what time
is it I don't know actually what what
time is it let me see the Rolex there's
the Rolex we get to the boys so it's six
six thirty in the afternoon so where's
the market I don't know I don't care
we're in the session right now but there
is no volume in the market so there's no
need to be glued in front of the
computer this is where you can take away
from the charts because the markets are
gonna go nowhere in this session this is
why I like to go back into the markets
around 9 10 10 30 night pre-lendon
session so we're gonna catch a Vibe
right now chill in the beach and then
we'll check back in pre-lending session
that's cool how does that song go I got
the horses in the bag or in the back
all right so market update so right now
camera is down it's got no battery got
no SIM card it's a long story maybe I
will one day
say it in a podcast yeah exactly what
happened but as of right now just woke
up about an hour or two ago you know
pretty much like the rest of the week
off uh the account right now is
currently sitting at 78 000 so I haven't
taken another trade since the loss on
Wednesday and yeah that's pretty much it
just one trade this week another problem
for the week and that's it so I'm gonna
be updating you guys on what the charts
did pretty much next week because it
doesn't look that good on this camera
like it looks super blurry and I don't
want it to be confusing so make sure to
tune in on week eight because now we're
gonna be turning these 80k into 160 000
so did you start hitting the six figure
Mark [__] starts getting serious
um but other than that I got a new chair
it's actually so uncomfortable this is
Shaq Shaquille O'Neal show show the
security on the back
so this is Shaquille O'Neal's share uh
chair I thought because you know he's a
big guy comfy guy but yeah like I'm too
small for this chair my feet barely uh
it's hit the floor so we gotta get
another one 500 chair so let's have a
recap of how this week went this is a
perfect example of how less is more in
trading you guys saw how we only took
two trades this week technically all we
just needed is one trade so we started
off the week with AUD CAD where we
entered these cells at the air
Adventures where I anticipated it at the
beginning of the week I explained to you
guys how I was looking to then hold the
trade to my take profit area where I
strongly believe that London session was
then going to take it to that zone I
obviously woke up and we were in much
more profit than anticipated to because
I never set the actual take profit
numbers on my phone because I would
defeat the whole purpose of Center
forget like our goal is to cut our
Lobster short but let our games run you
never want to cut your wins short
because that defeats the whole purpose
of the risk for award ratio like if
you're very confident on the trend of
the market you're gonna obviously make
more money so you just set it forget
then after that we took a small loss on
GDP cap just because I wanted to do the
same exact approach as we done in five
to six trades which is buying at the
same exact area of Interest so there's a
perfect example of how less is more and
that one trade alone doubled our account
where we hit our goal for ndk of the
week obviously the little loss in GDP
CAD wasn't a big deal but this shows you
how the risk management that I teach
with the set and forget strategy is so
precise and key and it wasn't only me
that caught these trades not only the
thousands of traders that are inside
swing trading lab that use my
certificate strategy but everybody else
as well in my Instagram Telegram and
Discord if you want to know more about
the center forget strategy just click
the link in the description below I have
a video that explains absolutely
everything what happens that come in and
in the first three months they're
generating anywhere from a thousand to a
thousand five hundred dollars a week
using my seven figure strategy so just
click the link in the description below
I have a video that explains exactly
what seven forget is you can see other
testimonials and many success stories
where I want you to be the next one
because the center forget strategy is
only getting started where it is
changing life to Traders every single
day so appreciate you guys watching the
video all the way to the end I will see
you next week we're going to be trying
to take these 80k to 160 000 so make
sure to hit that like And subscribe
button and I'll see you guys in the next
video